

#### **PROFILE**

Austin Coding Academy graduate with one year of working experience on an in-house built enterprise level e-commerce platform & CMS. Along with various other past experiences which help me in being a dynamic and understanding teammate! I am in search of an opportunity where I can apply my diverse background and skills to benefit a collaborative and inclusive team.

#### **EDUCATION**

Austin Coding Academy – September, 2018 - August, 2019: Full Stack JavaScript Kilgore College — May, 2013: Associates of Arts

# SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

Git, NodeJS, ES6, Javascript, CSS/SASS, React, Redux, AngularJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB, SQL, SqlServerManagementService (SSMS), VSCode, Visual Studio, Postman, IIS, Azure, CMS: DotNetNuke(DNN), Scrum Implementation.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

COMMUNITY MODERATOR, BIGCOMMERCE - NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- As the Developer Community Moderator @ BigCommerce, I provide assistance and act as a resource to developers and partners participating in the Developer Community. Along other members in our community, I'm also a person that developers and partners talk to about errors or problems they may come across with their development! Overall, my main goal is to make sure that the Developer Community is thriving with engaging, helpful discussions and ensuring questions are getting answered with timely and thorough responses!

JR FRONT END ENGINEER, CLARITY VENTURES — DECEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Daily: Workflows through Azure sprints, utilizing scrum practices, logging time to bill clients, completing FE tickets & communicating with fellow devs, PMs, and management.

## Accomplishments:

- Leading by example in content creation for new & current employees by uploading company stack overflow questions & answers, as well as creating internal documentation, training videos & teams wiki updates.
- Completing front end tickets on/ahead of time and being known as the most communicative developer within my team to our PMs on concerns, needs, successes and requirements/possible risks on change requests, especially when nee.
- Started communications and actionable items within my company on internal pain points, and being a voice for my teammates. Being a key member in the action of adopting a recognition program into the company, to help nurture the company culture.
- Always providing impactful feedback in sprint retros and within communications
- Company Stack: AngularJS, C#. Product: In-house E-commerce software & CMS(DNN).

SERVER, RAZZOOS — OCTOBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2019

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE (CSR), VISA — FEBRUARY 2018 - OCTOBER 2018

SALES REPRESENTATIVE, YODLE - WEB.COM — DECEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2017

My first position in the tech-world! Phone sales: cold calling, setting demo appointments, running and closing demos. My commitment to ethical sales kept my success high and my churn-rate extremely low. Sales lab leader for a new <u>web.com</u> product, after acquisition.

### **COMMUNITY**

Rocket.Build Hackathon — May, 2019 : Participant Youth Code Jam — February, 2019 : Volunteer